With Miko Seki, Sakuraba 46.
Hikaru Mukai.
We are here in our hometown, Fukuoka.
It's a cherry blossom trip where we are going to visit famous cherry blossom spots and introduce delicious food.
We have never been here together before, so we are looking forward to having fun and enjoying ourselves.
We are on the move.
Looking forward to the food. Kao Kao, gourmet food is delicious, isn't it?
It's famous, isn't it?
Maybe the ramen noodles at Ikabu, or the hiton-moikabu.
Smoke bone?
There's ramen at live catering events, too, isn't there?
Every year the members come and I'm torn between eating it first and enjoying it after rehearsal.
After the show.
I want them to eat it when they come.
We arrived at the restaurant.
I think people often say they ate yes chazuke on the tour in Fukuoka.
It's big, isn't it?
This is the restaurant we just visited.
Mr. Mushida.
This is my first time here.
It's my first time here.
Squid and stuff.
I'm looking forward to it.
Squid.
Here comes squid.
Squid!
Hello. Hello.
Thank you.
Gurgle.
I'd love to try some. Let's blow some squid too.
We're out of this side.
- Already halfway... gone? Almost there.
I knew it!
The squid down there...
- What? They say it's tempura.
- Sparkle!
It's turning into tempura.
- It's so good!
And the familiar...
- And the familiar "Thai chazuke".
- I'll have some.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no.
Yum!
Delicious.
Mmm.
168cm, the light looks like this
170cm person looks like this
175cm one looks like this
Thank you for the food
It was delicious!
Let's go to the next one!
I'm off to the radio now!
I'll do my best.
Let me introduce today's guests!
These two are from Sakurazaka 46.
Please introduce yourselves.
I'm Hikaru Morita from Sakurazaka 46.
I'm Seki Yoshiko.
Pleased to meet you.
Welcome back.
We're all from Fukuoka.
So we'd like to ask you to say what you think of Fukuoka
Please tell us what you think of Fukuoka.
I see.
Issei's
Ramen
New Year's Ramen
We visited RKB!
Ta-da!
Momopi is big!
So big!
So cute!
But still...
I'm home.
I'm home!
Pow!
Next...
Cherry blossom spot
Let's go!
We're at Aitzuru Park!
I haven't told you about it yet, but it's famous for cherry blossoms.
That's right.
We've heard about it, too.
We've heard about it.
That's right.
You should come.
Please come.
Today
I'd like to go to Aitzur Park.
I'd like to take a look around.
A little eye
LOL!
Flowers are flowers.
They're pretty and pinkish.
Yeah, they're pretty.Yeah, it's cute.
Cherry blossom color
Looks like cherry blossoms.
It's big.
Look.
It's going to be beautiful when it blooms.
This staircase here...
I heard it's a photo spot.
I wonder if they'll bloom.
morgen
This way. Full of date pavilions.
Do you remember the Grand Gold Medal?
The big gold medal for light?
When I was going to Tokyo after I passed the entrance exam.
So, you know, we were at the airport together.
We used to hang out together.
At the time, I thought she was really cute.
Oh, really?
I'm shy, so I can't really look at people's faces.
Look at Hikaru's face.
Yeah, her eyes.
I thought they were like cartoon eyes.
He had eyes.
I thought you had eyes the size of a comic book.
Yumi?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
For the audition.
The third round.
One before the last round.
I think Kyushu was in a different room.
Oh, yeah, yeah, something like that. In the back.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So I got there first.
And then Yumi came back.
Wow, you're on a different level!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Let's show them what we're going to do.
Oh, the top!
Top? Up here?
Looks like the top.
The keep.
There's Fukuoka Tower over there. You want to go?
Let's go there.
Oh, that's it!
That's good. I'm on it.
Let's get off the bike and go home.
Who's the member you're taking?
One.
Uh...
I don't know.
Maybe Rina Matsuda.
She's with me.
She's with him.
She said she can't help it. She's coming out from the side.
Yeah.
It's like, "Let's do our best.
That's true.
She'll cheer you up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Actually, you know, he's my captain.
My captain.
You can count on me, can't you?
I appreciate that.
I really do.
This single has a bonus video.
Oh!
That's right, the secret footage.
It's on the manager's phone.
You saw it a while ago, right?
Yes, yes, it was fun, wasn't it?
It was fun.
It made me nostalgic.
That's true.
There were so many images.
We were like...
I remember being there at that time.
I remember being in this place at this time.
It was nostalgic and fun.
But the fans...
"Oh, this is what I was doing at this time.
Behind the scenes.
That's right.
When your hair was this length...
At that time?
It's easy to predict.
I think.
After the Maizuru show...
Okay, now...
I'm off to Tahara for a con run.
Yay!
Hey!
Kawariko from Takase Station's here.
She's here!
Ta-da!
Let's go to Sakurazaka!
Yay!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
We have a corner!
Ta-da!
Here it is at last!
I'm so happy.Glad to hear it!
Go to sakuratabi in Fukuoka
It's over!
It was a great day!
Yeah.
I've lived in Fukuoka for a while.
I've never been to this place before.
Yeah, it was.
It was really fun to work together like this.
It was a lot of fun.
I was so happy.
I hope it reaches a lot of people.
Don't forget.
Thank you very much.
Yumiko Seki and
Congratulations Hikaru!
Bye bye